Guide to the Ohio State University, Office of the President (Harold Leroy Enarson) Records, 1940s-2002 RG.3.J
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
- Processed, 1971-1981; 54.0 Cubic feet; (45) cartons
  - Athletic Correspondence: Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 28)
  - Athletic Council: Decision-Making Procedures, 1980 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 29)
  - Athletic Council: Minutes, 1975-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 30)
  - Athletic Council: Procedures and Guidelines for Certification of Eligibility, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 31)
  - Athletic Council: Report: Academic Progress of Student Athletes, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 32)
  - Athletic Council: Report: Athletic Council Activities, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 33)
  - Athletic Council: Report: Women's Intercollegiate Athletics, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0005, Folder 34)
  - Athletics: Basketball: Correspondence, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 1)
  - Athletics: Basketball Search Committee, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 2)
  - Athletics: Budget: Proposed, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 3)
  - Athletics: Budget: Proposed, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 4)
  - Athletics: Chicago Tribune Questions Regarding Intercollegiate Athletics, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 5)
  - Athletics: Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 6)
  - Athletics: Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 7)
  - Athletics: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 8)
  - Athletics: Financial Statement, 1971 February-June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 9)
  - Athletics: Football Radio Broadcast Bid, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 10)
  - Athletics: Intercollegiate Conference: Report of Sources of Funds and Expenditures for Financial Assistance, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 11)
  - Athletics: Master Plan: Women's Intercollegiate Athletic Program, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 12)
  - Athletics: Michigan State University Investigation: OSU Related Players, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 13)
  - Athletics: Ohio State Basketball and WLWC 4, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 14)
  - Athletics: Outdoor Green Space, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 15)
  - Athletics: Radio and Television Contracts, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 16)
  - Athletics: Recreation Sports Advisory Council, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 17)
  - Athletics: Report: Academic Progress of Student Athletes, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 18)
  - Athletics: Report: A Brief Analysis of Title IX Compliance, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 19)
  - Athletics: Report: Feasibility of Increased Seating in Ohio Stadium, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 20)
  - Athletics: Report: Sources of Funds and Expenditures for Financial Assistance, 1970-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 21)
  - Athletics: Report: Sources of Funds and Expenditures for Financial Assistance, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 22)
  - Athletics: Women's Intercollegiate Athletics, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 23)
  - Athletics: Women's Intercollegiate Athletics, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 24)
  - Athletics: Report of the Athletic Council to the Faculty Council, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 25)
  - Athletics: Search: Director of Athletics, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 26)
  - Seat Coverings: Bids and Contract, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 27)
  - Seat Coverings: Smith, Inwood: Varsity "O", 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 28)
  - Seat Coverings: Sports Magazine: Contracts, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 29)
  - Seat Coverings: Television Contracts, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 30)
  - Seat Coverings: University Recreation and Intramural Sports Program, 1970-1971 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 31)
  - Attorney General, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0006, Folder 32)
  - Bakke, Allan Paul: Supreme Court Case: Regents of the University of California vs. Bakke: Briefs, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 1)
  - Bakke, Allan Paul: Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 2)
  - Bakke, Allan Paul: Newsclippings, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 3)
  - Bakke, Allan Paul: Reports, 1972-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 4)
  - Battelle Memorial Institute: Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 5)
  - Battelle Memorial Institute: Endorsement Program for Technology and Human Affairs, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 6)
  - Benefits, 1977-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 7)
  - Bicentennial Celebration, 1974-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 8)
  - Biennial Budget Request, 1976-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 9)
  - Biennal Budget Request, 1978-1981 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 10)
  - Biennal Budget Request, 1980-1983 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 11)
  - Biennium Budget Request, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 12)
  - Biennium Budget Request, 1974-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 13)
  - Big Ten Pacific Ten Meeting, 1979 August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 14)
  - Biological Sciences: College of: Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 15)
  - Biological Sciences: College of: Tassava's Experiments on Opossum, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 16)
  - Biomedical Graduate Student Forum: Program and Abstracts, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 17)
  - Black Studies: School of: Black Cultural Center, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 18)
  - Black Studies: School of: Black Enrollment, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 19)
  - Black Studies: School of: Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 20)
  - Black Studies: School of: Echols, Henry: Allegations, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 21)
  - Black Studies: School of: M.A. In Black Studies, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 22)
  - Black Studies: School of: Monthly Activity for July, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 23)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1972 July-November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 24)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1973 February-June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 25)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1973 September-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 26)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1974 February-June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0007, Folder 27)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1974 July-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0008, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1975 January-May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0008, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1975 June-November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0008, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees: Agenda, 1976 January-May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0008, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1976 July-September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0008, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1976 October-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0008, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1977 February-April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0008, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1977 June-July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0008, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1977 September-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0008, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1978 February-June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0009, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1978 July-September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0009, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1978 October-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0009, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1979 February-April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0009, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1979 May-July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0009, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees: Agendas, 1979 September-November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0009, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees: Committee Reports, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0009, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees: Committee Reports, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0009, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees: Committee Reports, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0009, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees: Correspondence (Incl. Reports), 1971-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0009, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees: Correspondence (Incl. Reports), 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0009, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees: Correspondence (Incl. Reports), 1975 January-November (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees: Correspondence (Incl. Reports), 1975 December-1976 July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees: Correspondence (Incl. Reports), 1976 August-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees: Correspondence (Incl. Reports), 1977 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees: Correspondence (Incl. Reports), 1977 June-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees: Correspondence (incl. Reports), 1978 January-June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees: Correspondence (Incl. Reports), 1978 July-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees: Correspondence (Incl. Reports), 1979 January-April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees: Correspondence (Incl. Reports), 1980 January-July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees: Correspondence (Incl. Reports), 1980 August-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees: Financial Matters: Correspondence, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees: Health Affairs, 1977-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees: Investments: South Africa, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees: Organization (Of OSU), 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees: Recognition Breakfast, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees: Recognition Dinner, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees: Salary Increase Statements, 1975 February (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 17)
  - Bookstore Discount: Proposed Abolition, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 18)
  - Bookstores: Report to the Committee On: Bowl Games: See Football, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 19)
  - Bowman, Edward H.: Report on "Corporate Social Responsibility and the Investor", 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 20)
  - Bowman, Edward H.: Selection Of, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 21)
  - Brooks, Dr. Keith: Dept. of Speech Communications: Confidential, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 22)
  - Buckeye Magazine, 1980 March-October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 23)
  - Budget: Current Funds, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 24)
  - Budget: Proposed: Highlights, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 25)
  - Budget: University: Director of, 1973 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 26)
  - Budget: University: Director of, 1973 February-April (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 27)
  - Budget: University: Director of, 1973 May-October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 28)
  - Budget: University: Director of, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0010, Folder 29)
  - Budget: University: Director of, 1979-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0011, Folder 1)
  - Budget: University: Director of: Budget Committee, 1971 November 15-1972 October 1 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0011, Folder 2)
  - Budget: University: Director of: Program Budget, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0011, Folder 3)
  - Budget Message, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0011, Folder 4)
  - Budget and Planning: Director of, 1977 January-May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0011, Folder 5)
  - Budget and Planning: Director of, 1977 June-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0011, Folder 6)
  - Budget and Planning: Director of, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0011, Folder 7)
  - Budget and Planning: Director of, 1979 June-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0011, Folder 8)
  - Budget and Planning: Director of, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0011, Folder 9)
  - Budget and Planning: Director of: Capital Improvements, 1977 August-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0011, Folder 10)
  - Budget and Planning: Director of: Rate Computation, 1980-1981 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0011, Folder 11)
  - Budget and Resources Planning: Office of: Director, 1974 January-March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0011, Folder 12)
  - Budget and Resources Planning: Office of: Director, 1974 April-May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0011, Folder 13)
  - Budget and Resources Planning: Office of: Director, 1974 June-August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0011, Folder 14)
  - Budget and Resources Planning: Office of: Director, 1974 September-October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0011, Folder 15)
  - Budget and Resources Planning: Office of: Director, 1974 November-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0011, Folder 16)
  - Budget and Resources Planning: Office of: Director, 1975 January-March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0011, Folder 17)
  - Budget and Resources Planning: Office of: Director, 1975 April-June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0012, Folder 1)
  - Budget and Resources Planning: Office of: Director, 1975 July-August (Box UA.RG.3.J.0012, Folder 2)
  - Budget and Resources Planning: Office of: Director, 1975 September-October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0012, Folder 3)
  - Budget and Resources Planning: Office of: Director, 1975 November-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0012, Folder 4)
  - Budget and Resources Planning: Office of: Director, 1976 March-July (Box UA.RG.3.J.0012, Folder 5)
  - Budget and Resources Planning: Office of: Director, 1976 August-December (Box UA.RG.3.J.0012, Folder 6)
  - Budget and Resources Planning: Report of the Task Force on Comparative Faculty Salary and Compensation Data, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0012, Folder 7)
  - Building Programs: Plans and Contracts, 1972-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0012, Folder 8)
  - Building Programs: University Hall Replica, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0012, Folder 9)
  - Building Space: Main Campus: Distribution and Growth Patterns, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0012, Folder 10)
  - Buildings: Improvements and Renovations, 1975-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0012, Folder 11)
  - Buildings: Naming of: Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0012, Folder 12)
  - Business and Administrations: Office of: Comprehensive Information Systems Planning: Five-Year Plan, 1977-1982 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0012, Folder 14)
  - Business and Administration: Office of: Reorganization of, 1978-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0012, Folder 15)
  - Business and Administration: Office of: Vice-President for: Correspondence and Reports, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0012, Folder 16)
  - Business and Administration: Office of: Vice-President for: Correspondence and Reports, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0012, Folder 17)
  - Buildings: Naming of: Policy on Naming University Facilities, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0012, Folder 13)
  - Business and Administration: Vice-President for: Correspondence and Reports, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0013, Folder 1)
  - Business and Administration: Vice-President for: Correspondence and Reports, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0013, Folder 2)
  - Business and Administration: Vice-President for: Correspondence and Reports, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0013, Folder 3)
  - Business and Administration: Vice-President for: Correspondence and Reports, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0013, Folder 4)
  - Business and Administration: Vice-President for: Correspondence and Reports: Jackson, Richard, 1979 May (Box UA.RG.3.J.0013, Folder 5)
  - Cabinet: Misc. Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0013, Folder 6)
  - Calendar, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0013, Folder 7)
  - Calendar, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0013, Folder 8)
  - Calendar, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0013, Folder 9)
  - Calendar, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0013, Folder 10)
  - Calendar, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0013, Folder 11)
  - Calendar, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0013, Folder 12)
  - Calendar, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0013, Folder 13)
  - Calendar, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0013, Folder 14)
  - Calendar, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0013, Folder 15)
  - Calendar, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 1)
  - Calendar Committee, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 2)
  - Campus Planning: Administration Building Remodeling, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 3)
  - Campus Planning: Architectural Historical Evaluations of Some University Buildings, 1977-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 4)
  - Campus Planning: Bicycle Paths and Parking, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 5)
  - Campus Planning: Biological Sciences Building Project, 1979 March 1 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 6)
  - Campus Planning: Campus Improvements Project, 1976-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 7)
  - Campus Planning: Correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 8)
  - Campus Planning: Credit Hours of Instruction, Autumn FTE of Staff, Expenditure Data, 1976 January 12 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 9)
  - Campus Planning: High Street Redevelopment, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 10)
  - Campus Planning: Location for Evening Programs Office, 1978 September 25 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 11)
  - Campus Planning: Location for the Morgue, 1974 August 7 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 12)
  - Campus Planning: Minutes of Meeting on Recreation, Physical Education, Intramural Facilities, 1974 August 8 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 13)
  - Campus Planning: On-Campus Directional Sign System, 1979 March (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 14)
  - Campus Planning: OSU Building Inventory Summary, 1979 June (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 15)
  - Campus Planning: OSU Community Relationships, 1979 January (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 16)
  - Campus Planning: Outdoor Improvements, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 17)
  - Campus Planning: Program of Requirements for Conversion of North and South Oval Drives, 1972 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 18)
  - Campus Planning: Program of Requirements for Page Hall Remodeling, 1976 September (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 19)
  - Campus Planning: Report on Adequacy of the Quantity of Building Space, 1974 February 1 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 20)
  - Campus Planning: Site Proposals for Recreation Facilities, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 21)
  - Campus Planning: Space Inventory, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 22)
  - Campus Planning: Space Relocation Plan for the Columbus Campus, 1973 August 17 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 23)
  - Campus Planning: Space Utilization, 1974-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 24)
  - Campus Planning: Student Services Bulletin, 1976-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 25)
  - Campus Planning: Summary of Proposed Capital Projects, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 26)
  - Campus Planning: University District Organization, 1973 October (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 27)
  - Campus Planning: West Campus Utilization, 1976 September 27 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 28)
  - Cancer Research: Articles of Incorporation: Ohio Cancer Hospital Foundation, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 29)
  - Cancer Research: Cancer Center Research Site Visit, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 30)
  - Cancer Research: Cancer Program, 1978 September 1 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 31)
  - Cancer Research: Capital Improvement Request for 1979-1985, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 32)
  - Cancer Research: Comprehensive Cancer Program Study, 1977 October 28 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 33)
  - Cancer Research: Comprehensive Master Plan, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 34)
  - Cancer Research: Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 35)
  - Cancer Research: OSU Cancer Research Center: Comments and Replies Regarding Summary Statement, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 36)
  - Cancer Research: OSU Cancer Research Center: Development Fund, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 37)
  - Cancer Research: OSU Cancer Research Center: Report: Current and Projected Space Requirements with Recommendations, 1976 March 15 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 38)
  - Cancer Research: OSU Cancer Research Center: Summary Statement, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 39)
  - Cancer Research: Preliminary Evaluation of the Financial Considerations of the Proposed Construction Program, 1977 November 11 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 40)
  - Cancer Research: Proposal for a Comprehensive Cancer Institute, 1978 August 21 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 41)
  - Capital Plan: Budget and Resources Planning, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 42)
  - Carnegie Commission, 1973-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 43)
  - Centennial Commission: Report of, And Related Correspondence, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 44)
  - Center for Lake Erie Area Research (CLEAR): Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 45)
  - Center for Lake Erie Area Research (CLEAR): Correspondence (Incl. Progress Report), 1971-1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 46)
  - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA): Sponsored Research, 1977-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 47)
  - Central Ohio Heart Association: Report of Research Review Committee, 1966 June 9 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 48)
  - Central Ohio Heart Association: Research and Fellowship Appraisal, 1965-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 49)
  - Chairs: Professorial, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 50)
  - Child Care Pilot Program: Request for Funds and Prospectus for Establishment of, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 51)
  - China Trip: Articles, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 52)
  - China Trip: Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 53)
  - Coal Research Laboratory Program: Proposal, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 54)
  - Cohen, Kalman (Dean, College of Business), 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0014, Folder 55)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1973-1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 1)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 2)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 3)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 4)
  - Collective Bargaining: New York Trip, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 5)
  - Collective Bargaining: Nurse's Dispute, 1979 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 6)
  - Columbus: City of: Center for Public Education, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 7)
  - Columbus: City of: College of Law Dispute, 1972-1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 8)
  - Columbus: City of: Correspondence between Enarson and Mayor Moody, 1973-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 9)
  - Columbus: City of: Expo 1992-Feasibility Committee, 1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 10)
  - Columbus: City of: High Street Development, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 11)
  - Columbus: City of: Police and Fire Safety, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 12)
  - Columbus Area Chamber of Commerce, 1974-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 13)
  - Columbus Foundation: Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 14)
  - Columbus Near Northside Historical District: Historic Designation for Old Student Union, 1976-1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 15)
  - Columbus Schools: Metropolitan Columbus Schools Committee (MCSC), 1976-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 16)
  - Columbus Technical Institute, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 17)
  - Commencement: Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 18)
  - Commencement: Moynihan, D.P., 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 19)
  - Commencement: Speeches, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 20)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation: Correspondence and Reports, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 21)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation: Correspondence and Reports, 1976-1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 22)
  - Committee on Institutional Cooperation: Correspondence and Reports, 1978-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 23)
  - Committees: University: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 24)
  - Comprehensive Master Plan: Health Sciences Center Component, 1977 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 25)
  - Comprehensive Plans: Guidelines and Definitions for, 1976 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 26)
  - Continuing Education: Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 27)
  - Continuing Education: Management Evaluation, 1971-1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 28)
  - Continuing Education: President's Statement, 1978 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 29)
  - Cooperative Extension Service: Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 30)
  - Cooperative Extension Service: Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 31)
  - Cooperative Extension Service: House Bill 110, 1975 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 32)
  - Cooperative Extension Service: Kottman's Presentation to Senate Finance Committee, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0015, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Commendations, 1973-1980 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Engagements, 1972 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Engagements, 1973 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Engagements, 1974 (Box UA.RG.3.J.0016, Folder 5)